[{"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 7, "question": "Mom, you're not wearing my clothes, are you?", "qSentId": 6}, {"answer": "Her personality, yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 36, "question": "Did you see a little you sprouting here?", "qSentId": 35}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 70, "question": "They said, well, whatever you see on TV with Sharon and Kelly and the others, underpinning it all, underpinning all the kind of caricature stuff that you have on the telly, actually you're very dedicated, determined family people, aren't you?", "qSentId": 69}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 95, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 94}, {"answer": "God, you have to be.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "Is it particularly important in somewhere like America and Hollywood in particular to be tough?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "Superstar?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "You're such an ass.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "That wasn't the restaurant that Sean Penn and Scarlet Johansson were in, was it, by any chance?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "It was that loud.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 130, "question": "Was it that loud?", "qSentId": 129}, {"answer": "Get out of here.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "Now talking of fighting losing battles, have either of you been invited to the royal wedding?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "All Brits want to go to the royal wedding, don't they?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 155, "question": "Wouldn't you like to go?", "qSentId": 154}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 161, "question": "Yes, but have you met the Prince William?", "qSentId": 160}, {"answer": "He's a lovely young -- a lovely, lovely young guy.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 166, "question": "What did you think of him?", "qSentId": 165}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 170, "question": "Have I been out with him?", "qSentId": 169}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 174, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 173}, {"answer": "That's a completely different level I can't even compare myself on because I don't have an entire country looking at me.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "Is it a particular pressure that only the kids of very famous people understand?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Amazing to have, you know, from now on her life will never be the same again ever in good and bad.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 197, "question": "For her who just come in to this family, just like Diana, huge pressure, isn't it?", "qSentId": 196}, {"answer": "Yes, I do.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 201, "question": "You know Fergie well, don't you?", "qSentId": 200}, {"answer": "To (INAUDIBLE).", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "Didn't you and Fergie do a weird thing in a restroom -- in a London restaurant one night?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "Yes, we were showing people into the ladies room.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 225, "question": "Did you go down and pretend to be restroom attendants?", "qSentId": 224}, {"answer": "I have a question.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 234, "question": "It's just -- I hope Kate Middleton can deal with it because it's going to be a phenomenal thing for her to have to try and cope with, isn't it?", "qSentId": 233}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 237, "question": "Why are we talking about this?", "qSentId": 236}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 239, "question": "Are you going to the wedding?", "qSentId": 238}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 259, "question": "You support them?", "qSentId": 258}, {"answer": "Because my mom has cancer and I'm clearly on drugs and it's horrible.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 285, "question": "Why?", "qSentId": 284}, {"answer": "For sure.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 291, "question": "And you were on drugs?", "qSentId": 290}, {"answer": "She's thinking, going, I was so skinny.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 310, "question": "You know what?", "qSentId": 309}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "But it would have been easy for them not to have dealt with all that crap that came into their lives without exposure of national television?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 366, "question": "Was it Kelly that stepped up?", "qSentId": 365}, {"answer": "No, we were already close.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 369, "question": "Is that when you two really bonded, do you think, in that period?", "qSentId": 368}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 373, "question": "Are you trying to make me cry?", "qSentId": 372}, {"answer": "At one point, yes, I did.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "Did you ever think you were going to die, Sharon?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, the one thing that you don't get is, as they're giving you a blood transfusion, I wish I had spent more time at work.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 391, "question": "When you reach that kind of abyss in your life, what's the reality about what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 390}, {"answer": "Well, basically I just was looking at my mom and I realized that she wasn't really responsive.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 402, "question": "What were you thinking?", "qSentId": 401}, {"answer": "It was one of the craziest things that I've ever seen in my life.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 421, "question": "When that happens, it's potentially fatal blow, isn't it?", "qSentId": 420}, {"answer": "It's very weird what happens because when you're badly injured, you get this adrenaline rush.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 426, "question": "And what was it like?", "qSentId": 425}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 436, "question": "This is back in England, isn't it?", "qSentId": 435}, {"answer": "And definitely this show changed me in so many ways.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 474, "question": "And suddenly it was glamour puss Kelly, you know?", "qSentId": 473}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 524, "question": "ORGAN: But if you're honest, when you look at magazines of other women with big asses on the beaches, I mean do you have a little laugh to yourself?", "qSentId": 523}, {"answer": "No, I don't.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 527, "question": "You don't enjoy the gossip?", "qSentId": 526}, {"answer": "No one's is.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 542, "question": "Are your lives not perfect, see there?", "qSentId": 541}, {"answer": "You know, Piers.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 550, "question": "How much of what I'm looking at is aux natural and how much has been crafted?", "qSentId": 549}, {"answer": "It was worth the money and made me feel good as a woman.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 560, "question": "When you see that, what do you think, the changing face of Sharon Osbourne?", "qSentId": 559}, {"answer": "I think I am.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 583, "question": "You are have a very glamorous woman for your age, aren't you?", "qSentId": 582}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 588, "question": "Out of being glamorous?", "qSentId": 587}, {"answer": "That's you on your show, the CBS show \"The Talk.\"", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 607, "question": "What did you say?", "qSentId": 606}, {"answer": "It's really inappropriate thing to say.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 624, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 623}, {"answer": "I think it's sad.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 642, "question": "ORGAN: What do you make of Charlie Sheen?", "qSentId": 641}, {"answer": "I think that he definitely suffers from some form of mania, because -- or -- I hate to use the word mental illness, but I don't think -- I think he's a very smart man.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 657, "question": "What do you think it is?", "qSentId": 656}, {"answer": "He has got to want it.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 664, "question": "Is that a template for what Charlie could do if he sorts his life out?", "qSentId": 663}, {"answer": "That I wanted to die.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 674, "question": "What was it for you in the end that stopped you continuing?", "qSentId": 673}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 720, "question": "What have I got on?", "qSentId": 719}, {"answer": "The breast look good.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 723, "question": "This was ten years ago?", "qSentId": 722}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 738, "question": "Well, that's half the thing, isn't it?", "qSentId": 737}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 748, "question": "Is that true?", "qSentId": 747}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "You like her, don't you?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "I did so much.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Very, very beautiful.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 806, "question": "ORGAN: Really?", "qSentId": 805}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 810, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 809}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 812, "question": "Well brought up, you think?", "qSentId": 811}, {"answer": "I don't have one.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 815, "question": "I've got to ask you this, how is your love life?", "qSentId": 814}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 817, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 816}, {"answer": "Pretty bad.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 821, "question": "Wouldn't you if you were me?", "qSentId": 820}, {"answer": "I met the infamous ex over that dinner that time.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "Wouldn't you if you were me?", "qSentId": 823}, {"answer": "Well, it hurts to get cheated on anyway.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "And it hurt you very much, didn't it?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "Couldn't get worse.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 830, "question": "That's not a good day, is it?", "qSentId": 829}, {"answer": "Is that why it hurt so much.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 836, "question": "Did I?", "qSentId": 835}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 845, "question": "Were you ever convinced that he was the guy?", "qSentId": 844}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 873, "question": "No?", "qSentId": 872}, {"answer": "Tweets and Twitter.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 880, "question": "What's that?", "qSentId": 879}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 887, "question": "What's going on?", "qSentId": 886}, {"answer": "I know I do.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 922, "question": "You have more than me, you see?", "qSentId": 921}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah, this is me at the dentist.", "docId": "110423pmt", "aSentId": 945, "question": "So many people are boring on Twitter, aren't they?", "qSentId": 944}]